now you just lost because it was also
whoever laughs first
I'll be at 30 yeah oh okay oh so you're
gonna like give us a cue or something oh
okay well you gotta go first I had no
problem with the staring but being quiet
for 30 seconds is an accomplishment
I just what's your favorite childhood
memory and why probably to like more
generally speaking just being together
as a family and like family road trips
thank you and mom really instilled bad
and us that you should be adventurous
and like piling into mom's minivan and
driving to Florida and going out to
California when Laura came in and just
like feeling really safe and free
I feel like generally like any time with
family it's just like a good memory for
me because it was important to you guys
and like it shaped me but I would say my
first memory that is that I can like
remember having as a little kid
and I'm only saying this because it
involves you is I remember being really
sick one night like super sick and
having a fever I don't know how old I
was but you like took me out of bed and
held me in your room like buying a big
dresser that you have and like just kept
rocking me back and forth and like
petting my head and I like I remember
that like I remember feeling really safe
it's my first memory and like probably
my it's like safe place memory well that
that's that's a good memory to have I'm
not sure I wouldn't think you could go
back quite that far but and I'm not sure
how far it is but that process that you
described happens from
when you were not necessarily you didn't
have to be sick for me to hold you close
that way yeah and I just just love you
but I remember like being really sick
and you're doing it I'm sure it happened
more times than that oh that's that's a
that's a certainly a pleasant memory for
me
I miss it hard to hold me now all right
right away if we get to the next
question all of the adventures were
we're not that easy for both of us she
doesn't talk about it but there were
occasions we went astray a little bit
and nothing serious the family
adventures who are fun indeed I'm sorry
when you when you think of the first
time we met what do you remember I guess
when you think of when I was born what's
here fuck yeah yes I still see you as an
infant as soon as you were born I was
there as as you know I have seven
children but before you my oldest four I
never saw being born
it just wasn't permitted then and
starting with Nick and then you and
Julie I did was in the room where the
birth took place so clearly that blessed
that first time I met you and some
babies but you know newborn babies it's
not their finest moment but you were
beautiful from the day that you were
born and I still could see your face
I've forgotten a lot of other things but
I still seated your face the day that
you were born it was it was a wonderful
occasion every child's birth is a
wonderful occasion
you were youth wishing your mom's first
child and that was special to her and
certainly was special to me
and hasn't changed you are still and
always will be special okay I don't have
anything to say about the first time we
went no mic yeah we just go back and
forth okay is sort of like the other one
but it's what's the most fun you've had
with me and why we went to Cedar Point
in Ohio with John Andrew and because you
were like a little kid I mean you were
like running around here on every roller
coaster you were like you were just
really happy and like just such a free
spirit and it was just a fun trip but
that's like that's my probably I
certainly remember that likewise it was
a fun experience besides you and Julie
your brother Nick was there your brother
John was there and then several of your
nieces and nephews and I just read you
say I was energetic and participating in
everything but what I also remember from
that trip I'm not sure I could do it
anymore but in those days I was able to
trick the like 50-something well like 20
years off or something like that oh they
were 20 years old yeah I remember
yeah whatever age I actually was we
could sort of figure it out it's
probably about maybe 15 years ago
no no quick 10 well anyway anyway they I
remember what age they guessed that
guessed 48 which may not seem like
that's doing anybody any favors but I
was told
years beyond that 58 so yeah that's
about what it was yeah so it was a fun
fun time yes I remember it well is your
turn all right I'm gonna just never know
if you're getting this but please edit
that out okay okay what do you think is
special about our relationship
I think the one word that would describe
but the most is respect we have plenty
of differences differences in just
opinions not that many of those and
sometimes differences or you know other
things certainly doing the planning of
your wedding we've had a few but mostly
I have like whatever you want to do you
know it stands almost exclusive had I've
done that and you're gonna have a
wonderful wedding but I of course I
respect you but I I believe in you okay
and with your six siblings blessed would
every one of them and said for them if
not all of them in their own way have
excelled you from the day that you
started interacting with other people
on children and adults which would have
been it wasn't the first time if that
happened but when you were at the child
care center the one that was associated
with the church and she spent a lot of
time in there's a very well-run center
but from that time till as recently as
when Anna when you visited with with
Anna and she her you know sent back
accolades commendations anytime anyone
interacts with you even for just a
little teeny bit they always come away
not just with her she's nice or
something like that but they come away
if it gets back to familiar to your mom
and oftentimes it does with superlatives
so you have always engendered that kind
of reaction in people it's something I
admire about you you have always
excelled
going back to the days mrs. niches class
where you were doing the presentations
and we would go over them together but
you never had a second problem in any of
your schoolwork or academics and through
college if there was any problem and
perhaps still now it's that you are so
concerned with perfection that sometimes
oftentimes it becomes stressful for you
but you have done nothing for your 30
years but distinguish yourself and I
have no doubt that whatever you do
whatever you attempt to do your getting
involved in the business now I have no
doubt that you will be successful and
always be as poised and personable and
nice as you are now do that in its
entirety like you're giving wedding
speeches okay talking to me nothing I
know I know they could always get it in
there I agree about but the respects all
right I feel like you think that I call
mom more than I call you but I I call
you just as much and I call you when I
like really need it like when I need
advice because I trust your opinion and
I value it and sometimes I call mom just
to kind of like I'm walking from one
spot to another so you know just
shooting a shit and I do that with you
too but it's differently when I call you
get really excited and then you like you
know if I have a problem or anything I
know that you're not treating me like a
little kid anymore like you're coming at
it from an adult perspective and you
treat me like an equal usually
and mom comes at it in a different way
both are good but I just I value that
relationship that it's more of a respect
rather than mom still sometimes sees me
as like a little kid or or like her
friend and I don't think that were I
don't know that we're we're friends but
in a different way it's almost like
we're equals and you just you have a lot
more respect I think and you show it
differently than mom does if that makes
sense
well thank you for that I have
absolutely no jealousy when there's
interaction between you and Julie and
your mom or even some of your other
siblings first of all she what raised
you single-handedly my job had me out of
town all the time it's not that I wasn't
a good father I think I was but I was
away a lot and one of the things that's
most pleasing to me now is the really
excellent relationship that you and
Julie have with your mom and sure we
talk when it's necessary we talk just
when we feel like talking and I know
you're in touch with your mom every you
know all the time and that's exactly as
it should be so I would hope that you
keep that up when you don't call
sometimes you're away or something
I mean I'll shrug my shoulders but she
misses it
what was the hardest thing for you about
being a father
well I had a lot of hardships as a
father not so much with you with Julie
but with your older siblings and
certainly going back to your four oldest
siblings who had the same mother and and
that was a terrible terrible
relationship that I had with her and
coming from a broken home myself and my
kids saying retrospectively it was a
mistake but long after that marriage was
completely gone I stayed because I
thought that was best for your four
older siblings I don't have any regrets
about that okay I don't avoid people who
aren't getting along should not be
together but they need to also make take
serious consideration of children if
they have them so parenting your four
older siblings under those circumstances
were as you can imagine extremely
difficult I tried to be a good father
and I think I was I think if if you
would talk to your older siblings which
I know you do they don't they don't hold
anything against me so it's not so much
that but the question was what was you
know most difficult and it would have
been those times I didn't have really
very much difficulty with you and Julie
Julie was did her academics on her own
terms but certainly neither one of you
from that from the day you were born
caused either your mother or me
any any aggravation or anything no it's
true it's really true doesn't mean that
you always did exactly what you're
totally right but lucky saying thank the
older kids broke you in mm yeah no I
knew then and I know now and I know
retrospectively what a all children are
good unless they are made to be
otherwise but some whether it's
hereditary your upbringing or
environment or what have you or less
troublesome let's just saying in others
in our new engineer you just learn I
mean there weren't any problems yeah and
I can't say that but it what have you
all do she thinks it knit yes but the
other four they're all they're all fine
now so that's that's that's the good
news it's my turn yeah I'm taking from
here right yep
all right what's the most ridiculous
thing I've done what did it teach you
about me so you're gonna tell me if
that's our choice I think we used to
have family barbecues and you would
break those bricks at their head it was
just the most ridiculous but I think at
the time I remember being horribly
embarrassed and I'm scared for you but
now looking back I appreciate it
because you just didn't care you just
you had this like thing that you needed
to prove that you at least looking back
I take it that you were strong enough to
still do this and
you were you could and it was a pretty
cool parlor check anyway
but I appreciate that about you because
you've done it you did it when when you
found out that you were sick and you
still went to China and you went up the
Great Wall and you had to climb it and I
remember fighting with you about it
before when we were in Zion National
Park and being so angry with you but I
guess don't like stems from the same
thing that you like need to show people
that you can do it and I have that in me
so I guess like me that's part of the
reason that it pisses me off and you do
it but when I like look back at it I
appreciate that like in those moments
you don't that like you're just you need
to prove it to yourself in to everyone
else and you don't just kind of sit
still and say like the doctor told me
that this isn't gonna happen so it just
won't still think it wasn't the best
idea but I kind of appreciate that you
think you're a cowboy sometimes well
more often than not if I did that
whatever the setting it was because
somebody asked me to do it okay it
wasn't the little kids that the food
asked we was doing with me no but it was
the adults and I didn't know I was
embarrassing anybody but you know I
would also admit that every now and then
whatever the occasion it wasn't just at
our barbecues like if I felt that this
was that I wanted to show off I would
want to chase me to break a brick or
something like that so I would be
responding to somebody who is looking
back now the fact that you're like 60
something-year-old father could smash a
brick with his head is what kind of a
kind of cool like I can say that I think
I probably could still do it I was it's
hard to find a brick around the house
that he wore your mom hides him but yeah
I mean if somebody asked me now I would
still do it
and when the time comes that I can't
anymore which is probably not that far
often so--but please know brick-breaking
I have to blow my nose get you'll be
able to edit that I'm sorry about that
it is allergy something triggering my
own okay okay what's the greatest lesson
I taught you and that's it that's a good
question the egg teaching the chicken or
the grasshopper teaching the what I've
learned from you is patience and poise
and at times I have that and sometimes
if I'm angry I may disguise it
deliberately or not not have it you
don't lose your you you do get stressed
and I mentioned that earlier because you
expect so much of yourself and you
expect such a level of organization that
when it's not happening you can become
stressed but you're always poised you're
always in control of yourself
you're always respectful of others now I
wouldn't say that you've taught me that
that's something I tried to instill in
all my children but then seeing that
reflected in you it makes me very very
proud so in my mind you're all but a
human a perfect human being in my mind
to a large degree I think that that's
more than in my mind but that's still in
the ibises of the b-and-b o beholder and
clearly there's some prejudice on my
part but you know you are for anybody
and myself included
I'm going to use a word that you
probably expected to be used anyway you
are the quintessential example of a just
a really good decent person
what are you hesitant to tell me now
that's a good one
I don't think there's anything I like
I'm pretty open and honest with you
anything that I haven't already told you
I think going into the wedding I was
hesitant to tell you how strongly I
didn't want to do it but I think at this
point that's already come and I think
I'm past that part and I'm excited I'm
happy for it but generally speaking I
feel like you know I don't certainly
feel that you withhold much from me so
that that comports with you know what I
perceive how am I most like you and how
does that scare you
oh well you have a lot of your mom in
you but you certainly have plenty of me
I think maybe the thing that I'd be most
concerned of a characteristic which I
know that we share is sensitivity yeah
and that's why sometimes when we are
talking we'll say something you to me or
I to you and it will disturb or hurt
even the other person the other party
and we probably you know oftentimes what
happens is we'll say something you could
text something and then realize you know
this was hurtful when I want to send
back and either explain it or apologize
but should either one of us be as
sensitive as we are I don't think either
one of us could be anything else but
that is I don't know that I've past
doing any traits to you not if you've
had all of them you'd have putti
negative traits but I don't perceive
that I've passed on any traits to you
that are
you know really negative or detrimental
to your your living your life that one
though I think is is an obvious to me I
think I have another one and it's only
with you
good stubbornness like anime beauty
comes from the sensitivity thing but you
like sometimes approach things as if
you're still negotiating like you're
still debating everything and it's a
battle and I get to a point where I just
I I want you to see my side of it and
you won't back down and oh it's so
stubborn and that's from you cuz mom
doesn't have it mom will just kind of
feel like okay you think by generally
speaking I only do it with you well I'm
certainly I don't wouldn't call it
argumentative but if I'm if I feel that
I'm because argumentative just implies
you just you know you're all I could
about everything like that it's more
like as if you're I mean I never saw you
in action at work but I can imagine I
mean your job was to basically to meet
with people and have them see your side
and sometimes you translate that into
your day-to-day life and you certainly
do that with your family because I think
we're a bit more forgiving and then
everyone else seems to just be like okay
dad that's fine yeah I engaged felonies
probably shouldn't I don't know that it
relates to anything so much that I did
at work from when I was growing up I was
if I had an opinion I was pretty pretty
much willing to stand by it go back a
far enough and then I grew up in a rough
neighborhood sometimes that would be did
the supporting my opinion might involved
you know a little physical interaction
but not more often and even as I was
going through school when I had an
opinion I would pretty much try to
defend it but others may not see me that
way and you may not but I see myself as
first of all
almost completely logical so that some
things have nothing to do with logic
just what you think but if somebody
proves me wrong I do back wolf now like
I do recall I don't know if it was you
or Julie I did one of one of you your
brothers and sisters and it might have
been several of you would say to me we
would get into a discussion because I
would say to all of you if you want to
do something or not do something you
know make your case yeah your mom would
just say no you can't do it sometimes
you know I would say no let's listen
right in those cases you're very
rational but every now and then in it's
not necessarily that setting but one of
you would say to me well you're not
being feared dad quote you lose your
using logic well I mean other than you
that said it but if it happened a few
times over your mom never said that she
probably thinks it my turn yeah I like
this game nut game I mean whatever it is
thank you
when or what was the toughest
relationship that took toughest moment
in your relationship in air it is air
yes thank you I think when I was leaving
for South America
you were just so deceivingly so
disappointed and the fact that I was
like had been going on this trajectory
that was so by-the-book and I had this
relationship and I had a good job
and I didn't really console with you or
mom I just did it for the most part it
was kind of like I'm booking this ticket
it was more of a courtesy call rather
than a discussion and I think I had
never really done that before and I
think I was probably scaring you a
little bit that I did it um we didn't
talk very much when I went you know come
with me to the airport and like even the
day before you were asking me if like I
would stay and I was like I already
booked a ticket and you said I'll pay
for you to not go and part of it I think
was ingest but I think you were not
happy with the decision that I made and
you didn't do a very good job of
covering that up which is fine but I the
feeling of disappointing you I think was
the hardest part well I think you
misinterpreted that it's not that I had
I mean you had a good job at the time I
had a good how you were fortunate enough
to have a good job right out of college
and you just gave that up
that was not my main concern because I I
knew that you could get any job you're
worried I mean as far as like being
supportive you weren't and I never had
you not be supportive you're usually
kind of like my biggest cheerleader and
you weren't in that moment and you
probably didn't realize it but it was
that was tough and I wasn't I didn't
want to have to convince you otherwise
because I understood where you were
coming from but I remember you saying
you know asking whether Sebastian and I
would say
together and I said I didn't know and if
we didn't then we weren't meant to be
together that this is something I had to
do and you didn't like that response and
you didn't like that he wasn't coming
and you were meant reminded me that beds
get cold when people are away I think of
what you said well and it ended up being
true I mean we weren't a good fit but
I'm gone I want had i not left i
wouldn't have realized that i wouldn't
be where I am now if I hadn't done it I
who knows where I would have been I
would have been happy well
retrospectively and I'm not sure I was
aware of all that you're saying now your
feelings but what I remember the most
wasn't so much a concern about how you
would you know get away with your career
I had complete faith in you with in that
respect I was concerned about your
well-being I was until the end and you
came back and again it's this is not
retrospective this actually happened
yeah I did raise a question about
whether relationship of I think it was
five years by that point you know
between two young people could survive
being away that wall so and and and as
you say now maybe that would have broken
up anyway but that actually did come to
pass 14 I currently needed to leave for
five months six months right now I have
no doubt that I would my relationship
would be fine I was with the wrong
person
neither do I okay that's them but but in
terms of Sebastian that's hindsight but
the other thing that in fact I did
predict was I was concerned for your
well-being in in two regards
unfortunately that came to pass you were
pretty seriously mom it's a fortunately
weren't injured but when you were in
Uruguay what do you require wouldn't it
okay Ecuador
and and then the other thing is that a
terrible terrible
I guess it was a fungus right yeah that
you had which was a major problem could
have actually cost your life in fact of
course I don't mean money-wise cost but
the major sin valve major surgery now
nobody necessarily could have predicted
that so I'm not saying you know what we
could walk out in the street right now I
got hit by a car
it was just like I've never felt more
sure about something in my life and when
I made that decision and you were so
against it and so obviously against it
and you're like use no filter it was
just it was tough you know you I want
you to be proud of me and I want you to
support things that I'm doing and that
was a moment when you didn't and I
understand I don't know how that would
feel and I understand where you're
coming from with all of it but as your
daughter as someone that had to like
hear some of that feedback a lot of it
being kind of cold was ah I'm very sorry
if that's either the way I was or the
way you perceived it I was very proud of
what you were doing and I would brag
about you all the time during that
six-month period and before and after
you know how you were you weren't
getting paid and you were really working
with negative native peoples and you you
know you were working for nonprofits and
you were you were not trying but you
didn't work helping people so I was very
proud of what you were doing I was also
proud that a young woman of weird 25 had
the was courageous enough to undertake a
venture like that in adventure and we
cool exactly being as negative as you
describe me but I'm not sounding that
that's where you perceive me but if so I
got over it very quickly I didn't
until you came back I didn't get over
you know being concerned for your
well-being but beyond that and of course
the thing with Sebastian that was
playing out as you were down there and
that that pretty obviously at this point
was meant to be but I was very proud of
you for what you did and I am I am now
I'm sorry if I didn't project that at
the proper time it's not to be Seavers
what did you learn from your parents
that you wish you could forget might be
a more appropriate question if I said
what what do you want to remember about
your parents and your upbringing now I
want to quickly qualify that my mother
who at a point in time was a single
mother of six at a time when women were
not very often in the workplace and
certainly not what six kids anyway and
my father would he wasn't totally out of
the picture but he he hardly supported
us and we didn't see him very often but
I mean we we were the fact that we were
as poor as we were I mean at least at a
time
I am my five siblings you know got
closer and because of that my mother was
a person that didn't have an evil bone
in her body not a mean bone
body my father let's finish what him was
not much of a father so I did learn from
him when I said earlier that I stayed
with a wife that really wasn't intended
that was more the course of going up
that way in that situation he abandoned
us so I wasn't going to do that to my
you know my kids my mother was nothing
if she wasn't the kindest most decent
person in the world but she had habits
that would just drive people crazy in
general and certainly drives me and my
brothers and sisters crazy I think we've
talked about some of them so I'll just
review one that to this day she had this
thing that if you drank water with your
food any meal anytime snack it was
unhealthy you should not be done so that
whatever food we have at any given time
we were permitted and then she would get
us tea kool-aid and any with just sugar
water and it's the worst thing for you
soda was certainly fine not water okay
until the day she died may she rest in
peace she never changed their mind on
that so you know growing up you don't
have to maybe when you're young enough
you just accept that your mother's
telling you they're at a point in time
something that's obviously so just
absolutely unacceptable
becomes a problematic when it keeps
coming back and back and back over and
over again so I'm just you know giving
one example I'm most most children
remember annoyances from their mothers
but I also remember is that without a
father she raised six of us
and I loved her dearly I'd miss her
I probably didn't always treat her as
well as I should have because of some of
these annoying things which would you
know as a young as a teenager and
preteen Andrew they're difficult to
accept so what was the question
yeah well I think I've given you a same
thing there's not I I think what it's
not a question of passing one if you're
talking about genes you you remind me
you're named after my mother and you
remind me of her you're a sweet and kind
in some sense you look like her new CD
teachers but some of those traits that
she had and certainly that my father had
we want to pay uh someone to anybody
what mistakes do you see me making that
you have also made what would you advise
me to do
um I think you're a little too hard on
yourself sometimes which you criticize
me for being we do it in different ways
but I think you're really worried that
your weren't good enough father or that
you made too many mistakes or that you
weren't around enough and then maybe
you'd be remembered like that and that's
just not the case and you're really hard
on yourself with that I think you should
cut yourself a break I think you're
pretty much ready to home with that I
also don't you know I'm not totally down
on myself I've used seven children
first of all with three different
mothers but the word half is never used
in our family and you're as close with
your half-sister lincei is you would be
with as you are with Julie who's your
full sister that's to your credit I'm
saying you like made us stay a family
and I don't know anyone else that could
say that or a few people I mean I know
siblings that are full that aren't as
close as we are and people make mistakes
you make any that are any other parent
wouldn't have made you're just you're
really hard on yourself about all of
that I don't think you should be well
I'm certainly not so so modest or hard
on myself that I wouldn't admit to that
and boast and brag about it even I do
feel that the closeness and the family
ties that the seven of you and
consequently my grandchildren your
nieces and nephews and and even the
great-grandchildren that's something
that was instilled in everybody and he's
pretty tough it dissipates it hasn't
happened yet
all of those people will be at your
wedding there's not a one of them you
know
I can't make it or this is that nobody
even thinks that they wouldn't be at
your wedding and and that's what kind of
family that you have and you wouldn't
think that you wouldn't be somebody
else's let's say serious you have said
in the past like regrets that you've had
about with raising any number of us and
I just I don't think you should have
them I mean you've said me we should
have been around more for Nick or you
shouldn't have been as hard on the older
for kids for any number of things and I
just you were a parent you were a young
parent and I just think that you made
mistakes as anyone would have but no one
sees you like that we all see you as a
really good father and we we recognize
the fact that we are so close as a
result of you telling us that family is
the most important and you should be
proud of that because we're proud of it
I am very proud of that I don't see
myself you know in a completely opposite
or negative if I don't see myself as a
terrible father I just have regrets that
as any or all of you we're growing up
that certain things could have been
right deal so it can't get that back I'm
certainly not I'm certainly pleased with
the products seven times over so that's
not the issue
oh you turned out to be yeah wonderful I
wouldn't change any one of you at all
maybe Goods girlfriend's boy I hope it
gets back to Glenn it's not anything I
haven't said to God but now other than
that I'm completely really completely
satisfied with the who all of you are so
in that regard I'm also not stupid I
have to take some credit for that
right but there are still plenty plenty
plenty regrets that I did do things or
didn't do things
you know could have done some things
differently yours or mine what quality
do you wish my fiance had but doesn't I
I know rich pretty well and if he has
qualities or doesn't have Galax
qualities that are important to him in
you in your life together I don't know
of them you know having said that there
is one courted turning around the
question but I've said this to you too
into him the one quality that he he does
have which perhaps at least your last
boyfriend didn't and consequently he
lost you okay now maybe that was meant
to be you know but he still hasn't
gotten over that you know it was too
late well okay and by the way as you
well know I did not I don't have
anything against Sebastian so it's it's
not that kind of a thing but what I
perceived is that he didn't I don't see
you as
okay Sebastian I won't use his specific
thing but because it actually
disappeared a couple other of your
boyfriend's too
and they didn't know what it it takes
for a man to please a woman and
presumably to hold on to that woman if
he wants to do that now if he's just
playing or doesn't care than they did
you know how much does it matter but in
the case of rich what I've observed
about him and what I believe is and will
be the case is that he loves you very
much
you don't want to lose him for sure but
he certainly does not want to lose you
and he's he's smart enough it's not just
you know mental smartness but he's
clever enough to do whatever it takes to
make sure that you do stay with him and
that was not necessarily a trait of his
predecessors and the result of it was
that you know they they did lose you and
of course I'm prejudiced about you but
I'd feel sorry for any man that loses
you it's just like he's a fighter and he
was just do you like makes it clear what
it is that he wants
and you like gorgeous for a team I was
I've never been a team like that before
it's different no it doesn't need to be
like a comparison between him and
everyone well what's the question
actually I turned around because I
really don't have any knowledge
I'm sure he has some faults don't we all
but I don't have any knowledge of any
faults and certainly none that have you
know come between you and him in your
relationship
what's something I could do that would
make you refuse to ever talk to me again
well
okay what's the one piece of advice you
have for me regarding a successful
marriage no I sort of touched on it
before but the implication is not that
rich or the main is the one that has the
total responsibility of making a
marriage work and what I really said
about him knowing how to keep a woman I
would say that about you too
in reference to him and did I said you
know you you want to keep him being once
keep you and if you want you want to
keep him then you it's not a question of
acquiescing or being bullied or anything
like that clearly those are unacceptable
behaviors but you should do everything
that's possible to make the person that
you love happy within reason okay
what have I done or what happened to me
that scared you the most
why because I said before that it was
something I appreciated about you sort
of but when you went to China and you
didn't listen to us and then you fell
that was scary but I mean I wish it
hadn't happened I don't know that I wish
you hadn't gone I think I just I don't
know you're you're not going anywhere
anytime soon but you are getting older
and that scares me and I just don't want
anything to happen to you so it just
felt reckless when you found out you
were sick and the doctor said for you to
stay and then you were like oh I need to
go to China
I need to do that and in a weird way I
can appreciate it I think I could at the
time even as I was fighting with you
about it but I just I knew if the tables
were turned you would never have
advocated for me to do that you would
have wanted me to start getting
treatment immediately and fix everything
and make it better and it was hard for
me to know that you that that wasn't
your first priority or maybe you just
you look felt like you were invincible
or something and it just scared me that
something was gonna happen and then when
you fell because like all the way worse
fear is happening at one time I think I
forgot what the question was what was
the question something I did that scared
you I think that was probably it
scared you yet this yeah I think just
you and again I understand it there
isn't even an explanation but I just
it's I think sometimes you don't put
your health first like when you hardly
ever get sick and so when you do you you
act like that you know like what you say
like I can never get sick or something
like that and it's just it's not the
case I mean it's funny when we're like
little kids and you say it but I'm not a
little kid anymore and when you're
actually sick and something could really
happen it just felt so selfish I think
in that moment that you left which is
not fair it wasn't fair of me to look at
it like that but I just if God forbid
something had happened to you
and you came back and the treatment had
started too late and something happened
and you weren't here I think it would
have been really hard for me to forgive
that I do appreciate what you're saying
of course you shared that opinion with
not so much your mom she was convinced
but your other siblings but I did act on
the advice of doctors I just didn't go
away as a renegade so I know just wasn't
the safest thing yes the accident I had
in China nothing to do with the other
you know that was just but that's still
sort of stems from the same thing it
still stems from you being stubborn and
like needing to climb to the top and
needing to do that and it's it's like a
downfall and a positive because I
appreciate that you do that and that you
are a fighter I mean I have that from
you a mom like you guys just fight when
everything was happening with my lung
and I like I remember how scared you
guys were and it was like we've flipped
roles I was like no it's gonna be fine I
have this it's taken care of I'm going
to I'm going into surgery tomorrow you
just need to hear that I mean I have
that from you guys and
I appreciate that quality but when the
tables are turned and it feels like you
like something really terrible could
have happened and I had no control over
it I didn't I mean what would I have
done if you weren't here you know
well I'm gratified by how you feel how
you felt that would be do whatever to
tell you what I don't care so it's not
that I wasn't aware of how all of you
felt but again I wasn't not to put us
through torture during that time well
you really didn't want to do that you
know that's the thing I understand why
you did it but it was awful like going
through it it was really scary like just
having that in the back of our heads
that you were delaying treatment and
then we knew like when the accident
happened and everything it's just it was
like our worst fears were like all
happening at the same time and it was
and then to have you come back and be
like feel like you would kind of like
basically seen death almost is like you
described it at that time it was just I
was so upset and like angry with you for
having done that and again looking back
it's everything worked out and it's hard
for me to like feel still feel that way
but I was it's one of a few times that I
was really angry with you for having
because it just felt so selfish well
your mom with me made the decision to
parcel out updates on my condition and
ward or not it was a she that made that
decision I think it was exactly the
appropriate thing to do now of course I
know what's going through you but yeah
but if I didn't how would you feel we've
had that discussion but under the
circumstances it wasn't like I was
around the corner where you know I
I was in China there was a lot anybody
could do it was just the decision to go
the other part of it was unforeseen but
the reason why you fell is the same
reason as to as like why you went it's
like you needed to just show that you
could do it that you were not strong and
sometimes I wish you would just do it
and you did do it and that's the point
like I I can appreciate it and it also
just frustrates me at the same time
because so much of it could have the
anxiety they like all of us went through
could have been avoided but I understand
why you did it I do I just well I just
wish it hadn't happened it was awful
I do understand I'm not gonna say if
something like that happened it would be
different because nothing like that's
going to happen anymore I was it's an
easy hollow promise to make but I can't
really say that in either of those
circumstances in the first case I had
specific permission by several doctors
okay they assured me that putting it off
for a few weeks was not going to worsen
the problem and I know how you felt your
mother felt that way too up to a point
then she just sort of backed off the
accident I had in China we were walking
a narrow line there I mean if I were
close to dying or something a problem we
even if your mom had from the beginning
and I shouldn't say if I were I perhaps
was at one point but you've got over it
quickly I wasn't I wasn't in danger and
a point of dying and if your mother had
publicized that from the get-go there
would been the next day seven or more
no trips to China point I see yeah I
don't say about missing the point it's
just like all of that happened and
that's fine it's just I wish you hadn't
done it I wish you hadn't made the
decision to go everything that happened
from there on is to totally it's
somewhat removed there's the fact that
you went I wish you hadn't done that I
wish you hadn't needed to take that risk
like I would hope that if something like
that ever happened again in your face
with that decision that you'd remember
that there are a lot of people that care
about you being here and if the tables
were turned and a doctor said you can
start treatment immediately or you can
start treatment in three weeks you'd
have me there the next second if I could
that's my point okay points what what
are you worried about for me and my
future I don't worry about a lot for you
because of past experiences and your
past performance I think you positioned
yourself career-wise to where you're
embarking in a you know a new venture
now but you you have your skills and
your experience and you've distinguished
yourself and just about everything
you've done so I don't worry that if
something happened with your you know
attempt at a business or anything else
you you always have the capacity to take
care of yourself so I don't really I
don't really worry about any of that I'm
worried about your health I know that
you take very good care of yourself but
I still worry about your health
and worry about your state of mind
worried that that you sometimes just
become overly stressed because you're
you know I've said this before but
you're so organized that when you know
something this big and the scheme of
things is amiss for you sometimes not
all the times it becomes a major cause
of stress and I worry about that I wish
you had the capacity to just dismiss it
just not to expect such perfection from
yourself but you usually get it from
yourself that's the thing it's not like
you know here's a sloppy person looking
for perfection you generally are pretty
much perfection like turn
that's for you thank you for first okay
what's one thing you've learned from my
relationships that you'll carry into
yours
family first I think like beyond I'm
seeking more broadly than you and mom
but I just I think I've learned from you
how the importance of family and keeping
everyone together and just unconditional
love because you have that usually when
someone really pisses you off and they
you know family and unconditional life
well if you've learned those two things
I'm a success what do you see in my
future ten years from now well let's
start with the obvious ten years from
now hmm five six kids grandchildren
no I think in 10 years I'll see at least
a grandchild maybe more and maybe not
but that that's what I would predict
I see continued success in whatever
[Music]
financial or business ventures you're
entering into because that tendency for
perfection that I described as sometimes
being a negative it's certainly not all
negative and you have demonstrated in
the past that you have the capacity to
distinguish yourself in anything that
you've tried to do and that's all
inclusive I don't recall ever your
having you know attempted to do
something and again not distinguishing
yourself yourself I recall your having
given some things up but not not
distinguishing yourself and of course
you know what I'm referring to
martial arts which you took you took it
to an extreme point you were very close
to the black belt you gave that up but
again I see only I see this relationship
that you have with rich as ideal I know
that you care about for him and I know
that he cares about you I don't have any
doubt of that and you have a good
support system you have a good you know
family support system a lot of it rich
has a you know decent family support
system and both of you are smart and
both of you will accomplish whatever you
want to accomplish to whatever degree
you want to accomplish so I see success
I see grandchildren I hope I see
happiness all the time